In foreign skies they fought for their country
Hurricane is a war, drama, action film directed by David Blair.
Polish pilots overcome prejudice to fight against the Luftwaffe with the Royal Air Force during the Second World
War, in the hope of protecting both Great Britain and their own Poland from the German advance.
Jan Zumbach, played by Iwan Rheon.
John Kent, played by Milo Gibson.
Phyllis Lambert, played by Stefanie Martini.
Cobra, played by Marcin Dorociński.
Josef, played by Kryštof Hádek.
Air Chief Marshal Sir Hugh Dowding, played by Nicholas Farrell.
Hurricane, also known as Hurricane: 303 Squadron, and as Mission of Honor in the United States (Polish: 303: Bitwa o Anglię), is a 2018 biographical
war film, produced by Krystian Kozlowski and Matthew Whyte, directed by David Blair, and written by Alastair Galbraith and Robert Ryan.
The film stars Iwan Rheon, with Milo Gibson, Stefanie Martini, Marcin
Dorociński, Kryštof Hádek and Christopher Jaciow in supporting roles.
Hurricane depicts the experiences of a group of Polish pilots of No.
303 Squadron RAF (Dywizjon 303) in the Battle of
Britain in the Second World War.
The film had its premiere in Warsaw, Poland on 17 August 2018.
It was released in the UK on the 7 September 2018.
The movie debuted at almost exactly the same time as the Polish production 303
Squadron, often leading to confusion between two films, especially in Poland.
The tone is emotional.